evhc.net 2018-12-23

# Privacy | EmCare Clinical Department Outsourcing | Envision Healthcare

## Introduction and Applicability

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. Evhc.net, by Envision Healthcare., (“Envision Healthcare” “Site,” “we,” or “us”), is very sensitive to privacy and security issues. We respect your privacy and know that you want us to keep the information you send to us secure. This Privacy and Security Policy (“Privacy Policy”), along with the evhc.net Site Usage Agreement, describe the terms and conditions under which we offer you access to evhc.net, associated sites and the services contained on those sites (“Services”).

This Privacy Policy applies to evhc.net which is owned or operated by Envision Healthcare. Envision Healthcare may share information among its affiliates, subsidiaries, or sites that it owns or controls in accordance with the practices set forth in this Privacy Policy. By using these services and this Site(s), you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use these services.

## Notification of Changes to This Privacy Policy

Envision Healthcare may modify this Privacy Policy at any time in its discretion. If we are going to materially change our Privacy Policy regarding the use of your personally identifiable information, we will post a notice that the Privacy Policy has changed on our Site for a period of 30 days following the change. Your continued use of evhc.net will indicate your acceptance of any material changes to the Privacy Policy.

## How We Use Personal Information We Collect About You

Certain evhc.net web sites provide visitors the opportunity to request information about Envision Healthcare’s services and may require the visitor to provide limited personal information (such as name, phone number and e-mail address) in order to allow a representative of Envision Healthcare, or one of its subsidiaries or affiliates, to contact the visitor. This Privacy Policy along with the evhc.net Site Usage Agreement describe the terms and conditions under which we offer you access to request information.

## Protecting Your Personal Information

We have reasonable and customary physical security (such as locks and alarm systems), electronic security (such as passwords and encryption methods), and procedural security methods (such as rules regarding the handling and use of information) in place designed to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Sites.

## Internet Information We Collect About You

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Site. Your IP address may also may be used to help identify visitors and to gather broad demographic information and to respond to legal requests.

## Information We Disclose About You

We will only share your personal information with third parties as permitted by this Privacy Policy (in its current or future form) and as otherwise permitted by law.

We share and give access to personal information to our employees and agents in the course of operating our business. For example, if you sent us an e-mail asking a question, we would provide your e-mail address to one of our employees or agents, along with your question, in order for that person to reply to your e-mail. We may share personal information with other Envision Healthcare subsidiaries or affiliates.

We also share and give access to personal information with other companies that we hire or collaborate with to perform services or functions on our behalf. For example, we may hire an outside company to help us send and manage e-mail, and in that case we might provide the outside company with your e-mail address and certain other information in order for them to send you an e-mail message on our behalf. Similarly, we may hire outside companies to host or operate some of our websites and related computers.

However, if we share or give access to information to outside companies we require them to use the personal information only for limited purposes, such as for sending you the e-mail in the example above. If you believe we or any company associated with Envision Healthcare has misused any of your information please contact us immediately and report such misuse.

We may share personal information if all or part of Envision Healthcare is sold, merged, dissolved, acquired, or in a similar transaction.

We may share personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law or regulation. We may cooperate with law enforcement authorities in investigating and prosecuting website visitors who violate our rules or engage in behavior that is harmful to other visitors or is illegal.

## Analytics & Customization Technology

We do not explicitly identify visitors to our Site unless they choose to identify themselves through requests for additional information. Like most web site operators, Envision Healthcare does collect non-personally identifying information that web browsers and servers typically make available such as:

  * Our websites may deposit a small file called a “cookie” on a visitor’s computer hard drive to personalize their experience or track aggregate site visitation statistics;
  * Our websites may use web beacons in combination with cookies to help Envision Healthcare identify and track usage of Envision Healthcare websites in order to gather aggregate data related to the usage and usability of Envision Healthcare websites. Envision Healthcare will use this “web analytics” data only as aggregate site visitation statistics or to personalize the end user experience.
  * Our websites may customize the website viewing experience and/or capture web analytics by using either internal analytics software or by sending this information to vendors to help Envision Healthcare analyze this data. Envision Healthcare has agreements with its vendors that they will not share or use the information for purposes other than to maintain and enhance the services they provide to Envision Healthcare.

Envision Healthcare’s purpose in collecting web analytics information is primarily to better understand how Envision Healthcare’s visitors use its websites and to optimize visitor experience and interaction with our websites.

Because non-personal information does not identify who you are, we do not limit the ways we may use or share non-personal information. For example, we may share non-personal information with our affiliates, suppliers, employees and agents, other businesses, and the government.

The visitor may disable your “cookie” information by adjusting their browser preferences on your personal computer at any time.

## General E-mail Communications

If you register your e-mail address with us, we use such information provided by you for internal purposes, and may send you information about new evhc.net site features, services, or updates, information about our company and promotional material or offers from some of our corporate partners, and other news.
